John Nam

Full-Stack Software Engineer

Contact

Jungwoo9543@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/johnnam1/ github/com/Tiranoe johninam.com

Education

July 2022- October 2022
General Assembly • Remote
Intensive Full-stack software
engineering immersive
program focused on product
development fundamentals,
OOP, MVC frameworks, and
data modeling.

May 2018
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in
Applied Mathematics •
Virginia Commonwealth
University • Richmond, VA

Technical Skills

Python JavaScript Django React

Express.js jQuery

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Others (Leadership, Teamwork, Problem-Solving)

Activities and Interests

Running Video Editing/Filming Travel Gaming

Certifications

CompTIA A+ AWS Cloud Practitioner Currently studying Security+

Profile

I am a Software Engineer with a background in Applied Mathematics and experience within the healthcare and IT industry. My interests generally lie in the areas of Backend Development and Full Stack Development. I enjoy the process of problem-solving and love learning about the underlying algorithmic solutions! My favorite languages are Python and JavaScript.

Experience

November 2021 – July 2022

Violations Processor Analyst • BusPatrol • Lorton, VA

Improved accuracy of statistical information by organizing, recording, and analyzing all data submitted through daily citations which led to increased overall efficiency and growth in revenue. Assisted QA team lead with meeting operational objectives by contributing data input and verifying that all documentations were correct and updated to always be ahead of project deadlines

January 2022 - October 2022

IT Specialist Tier I • Mindshift Technologies • Tysons, VA

Resolve product or service problems by clarifying the customer's issue; determining the cause of the problem; selecting and explaining the best solution to solve the problem; expediting correction or adjustment; following up to ensure resolution. Manage large amounts of incoming calls and record accurate, valid information through detailed notes

Projects

October 2022

AdventureTime • General Assembly • (Python, Django, PostgreSQL)

Built a full-stack application using Django with full CRUD functions. Included user authentication method with PSQL Database to update the model of the project. Worked solo.

September 2022

Travelizer • General Assembly • (JavaScript, React, API)

Built a full-stack application using React to fetch all data from Public API for the user to choose and favorite which countries they want to travel to. Worked solo.

August 2022

Instagram Cloning • General Assembly • (JavaScript, EJS, MongoDB)

Collaborated on 3-person team to deconstruct structure of current popular social media platform. Created multiple wireframes for project. Implemented Authorization method where user could login and connect to each profile. Assisted team to understand RESTful routes.

August 2022

Tamagotchi • General Assembly • (JavaScript, HTML, CSS)

Built fully functional Tamagotchi character with several interaction button for users to play the game to help character to survive